.
.
Sir,
سيد،
is there something wrong with the coffee?
هل هناك شيء خاطئ في القهوة؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Have I never said thank you to anyone?
ألم أقل لك شكراً لأحد من قبل؟
Sir, you don't have to,
سيدي ، لا داعي لذلك ،
Should I thank you all for your hard work?
هل يجب أن أشكركم جميعًا على عملكم الشاق؟
I think what Miss Su said makes some sense,
أعتقد أن ما قالته الآنسة سو منطقي ،
but you don't have to be too harsh on yourself.
لكن ليس عليك أن تكون قاسيًا جدًا على نفسك.
Is that why Bunny doesn't want to get close to me?
هل هذا هو السبب في أن الأرنب لا يريد الاقتراب مني؟
Maybe she just doesn't like living in a spacious house.
ربما لا تحب العيش في منزل واسع.
Do you have a warm house in our house?
هل لديك بيت دافئ في منزلنا؟
Yes.
نعم.
It seems that there's an old house
يبدو أن هناك منزلًا قديمًا
in Ouyang's house that's vacant.
في منزل أويانغ الشاغر.
By the way, sir,
بالمناسبة سيدي
you can use improving the teaching assistant's working environment as an excuse,
يمكنك استخدام تحسين بيئة عمل المساعد التدريسي كذريعة ،
Let Miss Su move in.
دع الآنسة سو تتحرك.
And we can look for clues
ويمكننا البحث عن أدلة
to the Heart of Stallone in the old mansion,
إلى قلب ستالون في القصر القديم ،
You can also use this to get close to Miss Su,
يمكنك أيضًا استخدام هذا للاقتراب من Miss Su ،
so like this,
هكذا مثل هذا ،
That is to say,
ذلك بالقول،
after finding the Heart of Stallone,
بعد العثور على قلب ستالون ،
The rabbit will take the initiative to throw itself into my arms.
سيأخذ الأرنب زمام المبادرة ليلقي بنفسه بين ذراعي.
Maybe it is.
ربما تكون.
Okay.
تمام.
Hey,
يا،
Miss Su,
ملكة جمال سو ،
have you finished your work?
هل أنهيت عملك؟
I've prepared a lavish dinner feast for you.
لقد أعددت لك وليمة عشاء فخمة.
We'll pick you up now.
سنقلك الآن.
Ouyang Yuchuan,
أويانغ يوتشوان ،
I'm telling you, no one likes your dinner.
أنا أخبرك ، لا أحد يحب عشاءك.
I'm going to eat something I like.
سأأكل شيئًا أحبه.
Besides, before you find the Heart of Stallone,
علاوة على ذلك ، قبل أن تجد قلب ستالون ،
don't bother me.
لا تزعجني.
Sir,
سيد،
it seems that Miss Su doesn't like lavish dinners.
يبدو أن الآنسة سو لا تحب العشاء الفخم.
Boss, it's the same.
إنه نفس الشيء يا رئيس.
Okay.
تمام.
Mr. Leng, why are you here?
سيد لينغ ، لماذا أنت هنا؟
Sit down
اجلس
The restaurant I eat is just a small fly restaurant.
المطعم الذي أتناوله هو مجرد مطعم ذباب صغير.
It's not suitable for a neat freak like you.
إنه ليس مناسبًا لشخص غريب الأطوار مثلك.
I'm not the kind of person who's obsessed with cleanliness when it comes to food.
أنا لست من النوع المهووس بالنظافة عندما يتعلق الأمر بالطعام.
All I know is,
كل ما اعرفه هو،
I like it here.
انا احب هذا المكان.
Really?
حقًا؟
I'm telling you,
أنا أخبرك،
I like this place the most, too.
أنا أحب هذا المكان أكثر أيضًا.
I think the food here is the best.
أعتقد أن الطعام هنا هو الأفضل.
Right?
يمين؟
I also think the food here is delicious.
أعتقد أيضًا أن الطعام هنا لذيذ.
Miss Su,
ملكة جمال سو ،
if you
اذا أنت
have time,
خذ وقتك،
We can come together more often.
يمكننا أن نجتمع في كثير من الأحيان.
Okay.
تمام.
That would be great.
هذا سيكون رائع.
That's great.
ذلك رائع.
Oh, by the way,
أه، بالمناسبة،
the rent,
الإيجار،
Keep it
إحتفظ به
It's just right.
إنه مجرد حق.
Okay. Where's the rent?
تمام.  أين الإيجار؟
I'll keep it for now.
سأحتفظ به الآن.
But let me make it clear,
لكن اسمحوا لي أن أوضح ،
for this meal,
لهذه الوجبة ،
I'll treat you.
سوف يعاملك.
Thank you, Mr. Leng, for paying the bill.
شكرا لك سيد لينغ لدفع الفاتورة.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
Coming.
آت.
Come on.
تعال.
-Enjoy. -Let me know if you need anything. -Okay. Thank
-يتمتع.  -اخبرني اذا احتجت شيئا.  -تمام.  شكر
you, Madam.
أنت سيدتي.
Thank you, boss. You're welcome. Wait,
شكرا لك يا رئيس.  على الرحب والسعة.  انتظر،
wait, wait, wait,
انتظر انتظر انتظر،
Wipe it.
امسحها.
Miss Su,
ملكة جمال سو ،
I heard that you're looking for something called the Heart of Stallone,
سمعت أنك تبحث عن شيء يسمى قلب ستالون ،
What is that?
ما هذا؟
Is it important?
هل هي مهمة؟
I don't know what it is.
لا اعلم ما هذا.
But it's important.
لكنها مهمة.
How important is it?
ما هي أهميتها؟
It's as important as life.
إنها مهمة مثل الحياة.
Hurry up and eat.
اسرع وتناول الطعام.
Brother,
أخ،
you're so unsympathetic.
أنت غير متعاطف جدا.
Ouyang Yuchuan,
أويانغ يوتشوان ،
what are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
To take Miss Su back to her residence, of course.
لأخذ الآنسة سو إلى محل إقامتها ، بالطبع.
Residence.
مسكن.
What place?
في أي مكان؟
I heard that Miss Su has been promoted
سمعت أنه تمت ترقية الآنسة سو
to administrative assistant professor.
لأستاذ مساعد إداري.
I even got a raise.
حتى أنني حصلت على علاوة.
As the best teaching assistants of Ouyang University,
كأفضل مساعدين تدريسيين في جامعة أويانغ ،
outstanding staff representatives should enjoy a better and better
يجب أن يتمتع ممثلو الموظفين المتميزون بأفضل وأفضل
living environment,
بيئة معيشية
Me,
أنا،
No need.
لا حاجة.
I have a clue.
لدي دليل.
It's about the Heart of Stallone,
إنه يتعلق بقلب ستالون ،
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Bunny,
الأرنب
this is the dorm specially prepared by the business school
هذا هو المسكن الذي تم إعداده خصيصًا من قبل كلية إدارة الأعمال
for teaching assistants with excellent working ability.
لمساعدي التدريس بقدرة عمل ممتازة.
Although the environment looks simple,
على الرغم من أن البيئة تبدو بسيطة ،
here,
هنا،
But it represents the glorious history of Ouyang's family.
لكنه يمثل التاريخ المجيد لعائلة أويانغ.
There have been so many years of ups and downs.
كانت هناك سنوات عديدة من الصعود والهبوط.